<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<emails>
    <email key="057324be-1b17-4017-9fd6-344e63fc53a0" id="new201@ISEA.com" title="Article 120: History of ISEA">
        <body>
|==-==-==|  /===-===\  |===-==|   /==-=\
   |  |     |===|      |=|       /=/  \=\
   |  |     |===-===\  |===-==|  |=|===|=|
 __|  |__       \===|  |=|       |=|   |=|
|==-==-==|  |==+===/   |===-==|  |=|   |=|
  International Space Exploration Agency  
                 news Box                 

Hi                               Everyone
This      is      ISEA      News      Box
This  is  Article  120:  History  of ISEA
We  are  today going to present  you  the 

H   H  I  SSSS  TTTTT  OOO   RRRR   Y   Y
H   H  I  S       T   O   O  R   R   Y Y 
HHHHH  I   SSS    T   O   O  RRRR     Y  
H   H  I      S   T   O   O  R R      Y  
H   H  I  SSSS    T    OOO   R  RR    Y  
                 Of ISEA                

The   history   of   ISEA   started  with 
THE       FOUNDATION       OF        GSEP
In 2027, a group of astronomist and     |
scientist  in  French Giana has started a
new   Space   Agency  called  GSEP   i.e. 
Gramhston's  Space   Exploration  Program 
with  honor to Gramhston, the head of the 
agency. They launch their first satellite
in  just  1  years  after  its formation.
It   went   into   lower   earth   orbit.
But     they     had     one      problem

They     Lacked    Money    and    crews.
And  they  found  out  a  Solution to it.
In 2029, they  made  their company public 
such  that  they  can take shares to make 
their  comany  grow.  And  the problem of 
man  power  was solved by providing their
scientists  and  any  worker   in   their 
company  good  level  of  insaurances and 
apartment  tickets  for  shelter engaging 
further     people     to     come    in.
And    they    got    profit   from   it.
They  got  upto  2  Million  $ by shares,
investment  and other ways of earning and
their  man  power  increased upto 2k with 
all  well  educated.  They  paid  all the
bonds              upto             2031.

The company unified other small space and
aero  startups  to  get  more  resources.



        </body>
    </email>
    <email key="45157047-13a7-42ca-bc52-68ca393395f7" id="nolangilmore07@ISEA.com" title="Invitation for Intestaller space travel">
        <body>
|==-==-==|  /===-===\  |===-==|   /==-=\
   |  |     |===|      |=|       /=/  \=\
   |  |     |===-===\  |===-==|  |=|===|=|
 __|  |__       \===|  |=|       |=|   |=|
|==-==-==|  |==+===/   |===-==|  |=|   |=|
  International Space Exploration Agency  
        
Date - 21 June 2150
Hi bro,
    I am Nolan Gilmore, your friend, and I have been working under ISEA for 2-4 years.
    I am pleased to inform you that the organisation has launched an Intestaller Space Travel Program.
    We are selecting Astronauts for this mission, and I would like to invite you to be a part of this groundbreaking journey.
    This program is made to take humanity as far as possible and to explore the unknown frontiers of space.
    The mission is estimated to start upto 2155, and we are looking for individuals who are passionate astronouts.
    If you are interested in joining this mission, please respond to this email with your details and qualifications.
    [32]Type [34]"rej"[32] To rejister for this project.[0]
    I look forward to hearing from you soon.
        </body>
    </email>
    <email key="fafc66cd-e36b-4551-9456-42005e513ccf" id="68363636406461726b2e636f6d" title="BlackMail">
        <body>
        Astronaut,
    You've been selected for the Intestaller Travel project. Congratulations? Hardly.
    You're being watched. Every move, every decision. This isn't just a mission—it's a trap
    wrapped in ambition.
    You have one way out. Resign. Now.
    Ignore this, and the consequences will unfold—quietly, irreversibly.
    Live or die. The choice is yours.
    To confirm your decision, type: choice 4c6976654f72446965
        </body>
    </email>
    <email key="d75d1256-84dc-44f5-b2c3-e2e14d133b93" id="nolangilmore07@ISEA.com" title="Help Me">
        <body>
        Hi Friend,
    I need your help. I'm trapped in a place I can't escape from, and I don't know how much longer I can hold on.
    Please, if you can hear this, come find me. I don't know where I am, but I think I'm in some kind of old building.
    There's a door that won't open, and I can hear strange noises outside. I'm scared,
    but I have to stay strong. Please, if you can, come and get me out of here.
    I don't know how much time I have left.
    Please, if you can, come and get us out of here.
    There are some people here they are ehwirr98j,
_________________________________________________________________________________
    AAAAAAAAAAAAAHHHHHHHH
_________________________________________________________________________________
    Hey, it's we, we told you to resign.
    We are watching you.
_________________________________________________________________________________
    [31]█▓▒░ NOLAN IS DEAD ░▒▓█[0]
    [90]>> Last heartbeat: 00:00:13[0]
    [31]>> Integrity breach detected...[0]
    [90]>> Location: Sector 7 - Unreachable[0]
    [34]>> Found aan image from Sector 7...[0]
    [90]>> Displaying image...[0]
    [32]>> use [34]"web-image 2f696d6167652f41414141414848482e706e67"[34] to view it[0]
        </body>
    </email>
</emails>